Father Mother Sister Brother is a comedy, drama film directed by Jim Jarmusch.
Three stories concerning the relationships between adult children, their somewhat distant parent (or parents), and each other: a reclusive father visited by his grown
children in the US, sisters visiting their novelist mother in Dublin, and adult twins called back to their Paris apartment to address a family tragedy.
Father, played by Tom Waits.
Jeff, played by Adam Driver.
Emily, played by Mayim Bialik.
Mother, played by Charlotte Rampling.
Timothea, played by Cate Blanchett.
Lilith, played by Vicky Krieps.
Father Mother Sister Brother is a 2025 comedy-drama anthology
film written and directed by Jim Jarmusch.
It follows three estranged family relationships in three different countries around the world, starring an ensemble cast that includes Tom
Waits, Adam Driver, Mayim Bialik, Charlotte Rampling, Cate Blanchett, Vicky Krieps, Sarah Greene, Indya Moore, and Luka Sabbat.
The film premiered in the main competition of the 82nd Venice International
Film Festival on August 31, 2025, where it won the Golden Lion.
It was theatrically released in the United States by Mubi on December 24, and will
be released in France by Les Films du Losange on January 7, 2026.
The film explores themes of new jersey, paris, france,
dublin, ireland, anthology, adult children.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.